Aisha's stock buzzing in trade the stock
is up almost 7 and 1 12% as we speak in
fact it also it touched the intraday
high of 10% worth of gain so solid solid
up move coming in for this
[Music]
one right Karan and that's not the only
one that's upbeat this morning we have a
Union Bank posting its q1 num some
really good cues coming out of there
decent credit growth maintenance of
asset quality and that stock definitely
being cheered by investors today as
[Music]
well and you also have that important
merger news in Focus uh ICI Lombards
board has approved the merger of par
acc's non-li uh business uh uh into
itself so that merger is something
that's keeping uh the stock in
Focus right Kara most definitely and so
much happening with respect to bonds in
bond yields we saw the bond yield prices
shoot up to around 6.5% in April they
fell 5.7 recently in July now they're up
again 21 bips in the last two sessions
and now again flirting with that 6% Mark
slightly above it going to show that the
yield has really shot up so consequently
the price of these bonds would have come
down considerably
[Music]